(Sheldon:)All get vasectomies so this
doesn't happen to us?
(Leonard:)Go out and celebrate.
(Leonard:)But not your worst idea.
(Amy:)Hey, let's go do something
to get your mind off this.
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah, we should go out.
Where?
(Penny:)Uh, I don't know, a bar?
(Bernadette:)Can't drink.
(Penny:)We can, but all right.
(Amy:)Are you hungry? How about
that sushi place you love?
(Bernadette:)Doctor said I can't have sushi.
(Penny:)Okay, look, we don't
have to go anywhere.
(Penny:)We can just, you know, stay here
and hang out in the hot tub.
(Bernadette:)Doctor said I can't
go in the hot tub.
(Amy:)Maybe you should
get a new doctor.
(Amy:)What, he said
you can't laugh either?
(Raj:)I'd like to propose a toast
to our friend, Howard...
(Raj:)his, um, his big heart,
his beautiful soul...
(Leonard:)And his tight little pants
(Leonard:)that somehow
did not make him sterile.
(All:)Cheers.
(Howard:)Well, look at this.